{
    "subject": "resource/Avant_Window_Navigator",
    "predicate": "ontology/license",
    "object": "resource/GNU_General_Public_License",
    "human_readable": "The license of Avant Window Navigator is GNU General Public License.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9807929992675781,
            "question": "What does the GNU General Public License permit regarding Avant Window Navigator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9052041172981262,
            "question": "What freedoms does the GNU General Public License grant to users of Avant Window Navigator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8158938884735107,
            "question": "What type of license is used for Avant Window Navigator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7152578830718994,
            "question": "Under which license can Avant Window Navigator be used and distributed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.649877667427063,
            "question": "Can modifications to Avant Window Navigator be legally shared under its current license?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6140884757041931,
            "question": "Is there any restriction on commercial use of Avant Window Navigator under its current license?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43011727929115295,
            "question": "Is there a cost associated with using Avant Window Navigator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41638094186782837,
            "question": "What are the terms and conditions associated with using Avant Window Navigator?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39055490493774414,
            "question": "How can you legally obtain a copy of Avant Window Navigator's source code?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3541840612888336,
            "question": "Is Avant Window Navigator open-source software?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The license of Avant Window Navigator is GNU General Public License.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7275_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can you legally obtain a copy of Avant Window Navigator's source code?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7275_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the terms and conditions associated with using Avant Window Navigator?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7275_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a cost associated with using Avant Window Navigator?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7275_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7275_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple because it mentions that \"The license of Avant Window Navigator may be customized, and plugins and applets are available... The license GNU General Public License 2.0 (Dock), GNU Lesser General Public License 2.1 (Library), Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 (unported) (images)\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the licensing of Avant Window Navigator (AWN), stating that it is licensed under the GNU General Public License, along with other licenses. Therefore, the statement \"The license of Avant Window Navigator is GNU General Public License\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}